find a comfortable position close your eyes and enter your level
by yourself
using the three -to -one method followed by a ten to one
countdown I will then come in after that with some positive
statements and affirmations take your time
Thank you.
Relax.
Take a deep breath and as you exhale relax and go deeper.
You will continue to listen to my voice. you will continue to
follow the instructions at this level of the mind or any other
level including the outer conscious level this is for your
benefit you desire it and it is so
the difference between genius mentality and lay mentality is
that geniuses use more of their their minds and use them in
a special manner.
You are now learning to use more of your mind and to
use it in a special manner.
The following are beneficial statements that you may
occasionally repeat while at these levels of the mind. repeat
mentally after me my increasing mental faculties are for serving
humanity better
every day in every way I am getting better better and better
Positive thoughts, suggestions and images bring me benefits and
advantages I desire.
I have full control and complete dominion over my sensing
faculties at all levels of the mind.
I will always maintain a perfectly healthy body, mind and immune
system
Take a deep breath, relax and go deeper and continue to breathe
deeply, slowly and rhythmically throughout the entire exercise.
exercise.
Now mentally focus on one of your hands as your palms rest
on your lap.
Move move your awareness closer and closer to your hand and
imagine the hand getting larger and larger as you move closer
observe the skin covering your hand from close up
Imagine the tiny hairs growing out from that part of your hand.
Get closer and closer and focus your attention on one cell of
your hand.
and imagine what shape does it have.
Move closer and closer and enter the cell itself.
What do you imagine inside the cell of your hand?
Hold a nucleus in your hands.
What do you sense?
Make the nucleus larger and go within the nucleus.
Whatever you sense with your imagination you can use as a point
of reference in the future.
Now imagine the strands of chromosomes of that cell within the
nucleus.
Continue to go closer and closer to the DNA molecules that make
up this very tiny expression of you. you.
Closer and deeper, you can see that the molecule is comprised of
atoms.
Moving closer to an atom, notice the electrons that are
encircling the nucleus of the atom.
And as you move closer, notice the subatomic particles of the
atom.
And now notice the energy that makes up the atom begins to
expand around you, becoming larger and larger so that you find
yourself in a seemingly infinite space
at this dimension you exist as a part of a vast and
complex system it is a part part of you, and you are
part of it.
Now begin to come back, sensing the electrons, the atoms, now
the atoms forming together to make molecules. molecules.
Moving back to the molecules forming the chromosomes in the
nucleus.
Now with your imagination, move away from the nucleus, farther
and farther out, and now observe the cell once again continue to
move farther and farther out and observe the tiny hairs on your
hand and now your entire hand
continue moving farther and farther out and observe yourself
from above
farther and farther out and observe the entire room move your
awareness farther out to observe the building you are in
Continue going farther and farther out and now observe the city
you live in
Trees, nearby buildings and roads, highways
Are there any landmarks or special features?
Continue moving farther and farther out and observe the state
you live in.
And now the country And now the continent
You can observe the curvature of the planet Continue moving
farther out and observe your your planet completely.
Continue moving farther out and now observe your solar system
completely.
Imagine the solar system getting smaller and smaller until you
can see our star, the Sun, as one of hundreds of billions
of stars in our galaxy as if stars were the atoms that
make larger molecules the billions of galaxies as if perhaps our
own solar system is a tiny subatomic particle in the body of
the universe
As you hold in your consciousness all of these different levels,
it can be useful to remember that we do exist on all
these levels.
From this perspective, notice how you are one with everything
that is and there is greatness in your existence.
Now slowly begin your journey back. back.
You can observe our solar system from a distance.
The planets.
Closer and closer now.
You can observe our beautiful planet Earth.
Move closer and closer.
And notice What is the continent you live in, the country you
live in,
the state, the city, the building building you are in, the room
you are in, and now be one with yourself once again.
Whatever you perceive with your imagination at this dimension,
you can use as points of reference in the future.
It is now a fact that subjective points of reference have been
established.
To function at these levels and to use these points of
reference, all you need is a sincere desire to solve problems.
your mind will automatically seek out these points of reference
where you will perceive and to become aware of information you
can use to solve such problems and this is so
think back on your experience going from the microcosm to the
macrocosm and think of where you are in the whole scheme of
things as you grow and are challenged with life's ups and downs
know that there are answers to all your problems in the universe
all you need to do is seek them
every time you function at these levels of the mind you will
receive beneficial effects physically and mentally you may use
these levels of the mind to help yourself physically and
mentally you may use these levels of the mind to help your
loved ones physically and mentally you may use these levels of
the mind to help any human being who needs help physically and
mentally you will always use these levels of the mind in a
constructive creative manner for all that is good honest pure
clean and positive and this is so you will continue to strive
to take part in constructive and creative activities to make
this a better world to live in so that when you move
on you You shall have left behind a better world for those
who follow.
You will consider the whole of humanity, depending on their
ages, as fathers or mothers, brothers or sisters, sons or
daughters.
You are a superior human being. You have greater understanding,
compassion, and patience with others.
In a moment, I'm going to count from 1 to 5 and
cause a sound with my fingers.
At that moment, you will open your eyes, be wide awake, feeling
fine and in perfect health, feeling better than before.
Vision, eyesight and hearing improve every time you function at
these levels of the mind.
1, 2, coming out slowly now, 3, at the count of 5,
you will open your eyes, be wide awake,
feeling fine and in perfect health, feeling better than before,
feeling the way you feel Feel when you have slept the right
amount of revitalizing, refreshing, relaxing, healthy sleep.
4, 5, eyes open, wide awake, feeling fine and in perfect health,
feeling better than before.